Guide to the School of Hotel Administration Dean's records, 1981-2012.
School of Hotel Administration Dean's records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
School of Hotel Administration Dean's records, 1981-2012.
28-1-4069
Cornell University. School of Hotel Administration. Dean.
45 cubic feet.
Correspondence, printed materials.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes correspondence, reports, meeting minutes, distinguished speaker lists, photographs, subject files, and other records of the School of Hotel Administration, particularly pertaining to the Office of the Dean.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes correspondence, reports, meeting minutes, distinguished speaker lists, photographs, subject files, and other records of the School of Hotel Administration, particularly pertaining to the Office of the Dean.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University -- Faculty.
Subjects:
Hotel management -- Study and teaching.; Hotel management schools -- New York (State) -- Ithaca.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of the office of origin.
Closed for research until 2016.
CONTAINER LIST
- Dean's Correspondence (A-R), 1984 (Box 1)
- Dean's Correspondence (S-Z), 1984 (Box 2)
- Dean's Chron Files, 1986 (Box 2)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 3)
- Dean Clark Chron Files, 1985 (Box 4)
- Statler Inn Records, 1983-1987 (Box 4)
- Statler Hotel Records, 1985-1990 (Box 4)
- Statler West Records (Box 4)
- National Society of Minority Hoteliers, 1987-1991 (Box 4)
- Real Estate Conference, 1980-1990 (Box 4)
- Real Estate Council, 1982-1990 (Box 4)
- Cornell H.R.A. Quarterly Records, 1983-1988 (Box 4)
- Subject Files (Box 5)
- Dean Clark Correspondence, 1985 (Box 6)
- Past Cookies Speakers, 1980-1986 (Box 7)
- Former Faculty Information - LTS (Box 8)
- Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 9)
- GIK Linens/Baker Linen (Box 10)
- GIK AV Equipment/SONY (Box 10)
- GIK AV Equipment/Mitsubishi (Box 10)
- GIK Bedding/Serta (Box 10)
- GIK Mirrors/Rice Co. (Box 10)
- GIK Refrigerators/Domestic (Box 10)
- GIK Shelving/Metropolitan Wire Goods (Box 10)
- GIK tables/Howe Co. (Box 10)
- GIK Correspondence (Box 10)
- GIK Meeting Minutes Fund Development (Box 10)
- GIK Accessories Pending/SHIP'N'OUT (Box 10)
- GIK Carpet/THAI PING (Box 10)
- GIK China/Buffalo China (Box 10)
- GIK Bar Control System/Accardis (Box 10)
- GIK China/Syracuse China (Box 10)
- GIK Supplies/Rubbermaid (Box 10)
- GIK Committee (Box 10)
- Fund Development Correspondence (Box 10)
- GIK Food Facilities Resources (Box 10)
- Fund Development Donor Recognition (Box 10)
- Statler Donor Recognition (Box 10)
- Statler Project Systems Briefs (Box 10)
- Statler Program (Box 10)
- Statler Budget Item Classification (Box 10)
- Names and Information (Box 10)
- Project Costs - Current (Box 10)
- Project Costs - Superseded (Box 10)
- Organization Charts (Box 10)
- Architect's Contract: Goody-Clancy (Box 10)
- Lehrer McGovern Construction Managers (Box 10)
- Lehrer McGovern Contract Form-General Conditions (Box 10)
- AV Services (Box 10)
- Planning Program Plans (Box 10)
- Contract With Wilke AV Consultant (Box 10)
- Statler Minutes - TAC Architect (Box 10)
- Statler Minutes - Hurd/Assoc Interior Design (Box 10)
- Statler Minutes - Lehrer McGovern pt 1 (Box 10)
- Statler Minutes - Lehrer McGovern pt 2 (Box 10)
- Statler Minutes - CU Architectural Services (Box 10)
- Statler Minutes - Policy Meeting (Box 10)
- Statler Minutes - Project Building Committee (Box 10)
- GIK Signs - Spencer Industries (Box 10)
- Statler Artwork (Box 10)
- Computer Systems Briefs (Box 10)
- Statler Minutes - AV Equipment (Box 10)
- Parking (Box 10)
- Mock Ups and Plans (Box 10)
- Renderings (Box 10)
- Procurement Services Agreement (Box 10)
- Correspondence (Box 10)
- Amfort (Box 11)
- American Express Foundation (Box 11)
- Asta/Pata, 1981-1989 (Box 11)
- China (Miscellaneous, John Clark) CIA, 1985-1989 (Box 11)
- Dominican Republic (John Clark) (Box 11)
- Academic Deficiency, 1987-1989 (Box 12)
- Computer Services, 1983-1988 (Box 12)
- Academic Integrity, 1991 (Box 12)
- Accessory Instruction, 1986-1987 (Box 12)
- Annual Reports, 1962-1989 (Box 12)
- Binenkorb Computer Center, 1982-1989 (Box 12)
- Career Services, 1983-1990 (Box 12)
- Area Coordinators, 1981-1988 (Box 12)
- CSH, 1989-1990 (Box 12)
- COSEP, 1979-1984 (Box 12)
- CRTF, 1985 (Box 12)
- Delphi Study, 1984 (Box 12)
- Hospitality News, 1988-1989 (Box 12)
- Library Archive Project, 1987-1990 (Box 12)
- Minority Affairs, 1983-1988 (Box 12)
- Industry Speaker Forum, 1981-1990 (Box 12)
- SHA History Book Materials: (Box 13)
- Endnote Files (Box 13)
- Oral Interviews (Box 13)
- Copies of Photos (Box 13)
- Other Hotel Schools, Foreign and Domestic - Miscellaneous (Box 14)
- CMI (Box 14)
- IHA (Box 14)
- Lodging Magazine (Box 14)
- NCR (Box 14)
- NAA (Box 14)
- Cornell University Minority Educational Council, 1984-1988 (Box 14)
- Cornell University Presidents Fund for Educational Initiatives, 1987-1989 (Box 14)
- Civil Action Suit - Shreve (Box 15)
- Fleming Report (Box 15)
- Home Study Program (Box 15)
- Cornell University 125th Anniversary (Box 15)
- Casino Course - D. Whitehead (Box 15)
- Properties Management (Box 15)
- Cornell University Policy Statements (Box 15)
- Annual Reports (Box 15)
- Statler Chain Recipes (Box 15)
- American Hotel Foundation (Box 16)
- Horwath Asia Pacific Conference, 1993 (Box 16)
- Kaga City Lectures (Box 16)
- City Symposium HEC (Box 16)
- HEC 54 (Box 16)
- HEC 56 (Box 16)
- HEC 57 (Box 16)
- HEC 59, 1984 (Box 16)
- HEC 60, 1985 (Box 16)
- HEC 61, 1986 (Box 16)
- HEC 62, 1987 (Box 16)
- HEC 63, 1988 (Box 16)
- HEC 64, 1989 (Box 16)
- HEC 64 Opening Articles (Box 16)
- HEC 64 Roundtable (Box 16)
- Puerto Rico Branch (Box 16)
- Unit Plan (Box 17)
- TRIAD, 1971-1975 (Box 17)
- SHA TRIAD (Box 17)
- AH and MA Economy Lodging Conference Reference Materials, 1993 (Box 17)
- AH and MA Articles on Economy Lodging (Box 17)
- Smith Travel Research (Box 17)
- Dean's Draft (Box 17)
- Forecasts (Box 17)
- Speech Text with Slide Mockups (Box 17)
- Dean's Notes and Miscellaneous Material (Box 17)
- Taxes and Labor Trends (Box 17)
- Brands (Box 17)
- Seniors (Box 17)
- Correspondence A-Z, 1990-1993 (Box 18)
- Speech Dynamics (Box 19)
- Club Med Bermuda (Box 19)
- Ajman University (Box 19)
- Dans of Israel Dorsey (Box 19)
- Whitney (Box 19)
- European Institute of Tourism Management (Box 19)
- Haaga Institute (Box 19)
- Phipps Community Development Corporation (Box 19)
- Spectacor Management Group (Box 19)
- Past HECs (Box 19)
- HEC 65 (Box 19)
- HEC 66 (Box 19)
- HEC 67 (Box 19)
- HEC 68 (Box 19)
- HEC 69 (Box 19)
- History (Box 20)
- American Center Wine Food and Arts Board Books, 1999 (Box 21)
- American Center Wine Food and Arts Board Books, 1998 (Box 21)
- American Center Wine Food and Arts Board Books, 1997 (Box 21)
- American Center Wine Food and Arts Board Books, 1996 (Box 21)
- Exhibition Concept Report (Box 21)
- School of Hotel Administration Advisory Board Meeting, 1999 (Box 21)
- School of Hotel Administration Advisory Board Meeting, 1998 (Box 21)
- School of Hotel Administration Advisory Board Meeting, 1997 (Box 21)
- School of Hotel Administration Advisory Board Meeting, 1996 (Box 21)
- School of Hotel Administration Advisory Board Meeting, 1995 (Box 21)
- Distant Learning and Resource Coordination Sub Committee Notebook (Box 21)
- Australian International Hotel School Advisory Board, 1997 (Box 22)
- Australian International Hotel School Advisory Board, 1998 (Box 22)
- Australian International Hotel School Advisory Board, 1999 (Box 22)
- Australian International Hotel School: (Box 23)
- Strategic Direction (Box 23)
- Academic Review, 1999 (Box 23)
- School Bill (Box 23)
- RMIT Agreement (Box 23)
- Memos to the Board of Management (Box 23)
- Financial (Box 23)
- Statements - Arrangements - Payments (Box 23)
- Dittman Working File (Box 23)
- Monitoring Report (Box 23)
- Agreement - Letter of Intent - Confidential (Box 23)
- Deed (Box 23)
- Dittman Letter to Mick (Box 23)
- Lilley Faculty (Box 23)
- Development Plan (Box 23)
- Curriculum Review (Box 23)
- Conferring of Degrees (Box 23)
- Conlin visit to SHA, 1997 (Box 23)
- Bio's and Business (Box 23)
- Cards Annual (Box 23)
- Reports (Box 23)
- Admissions (Box 23)
- Reports (Box 23)
- Correspondence, 1997 (Box 23)
- Correspondence, 1998 (Box 23)
- Video AIHS Graduation, 1997 (Box 23)
- CU Academic Leadership Documentation (Box 24)
- CU Asia Strategy Group Correspondence and Board Meeting Materials (Box 24)
- Chinese University Of Hong Kong Documents - Correspondence (Box 24)
- Dean's Distinguished Speaker List:, 1988 (Box 25)
- - Thomas Rohr (Box 25)
- - Jeffrey Baer (Box 25)
- - Andrew Raubeson (Box 25)
- - Susan Shellenberger (Box 25)
- - Carl Mottek (Box 25)
- - Robert Weller (Box 25)
- - Barry Conrad (Box 25)
- - Robert Small (Box 25)
- Dean's Distinguished Speaker List, 1989 (Box 25)
- - Drew Nieporent (Box 25)
- - Albert Ehringer (Box 25)
- - James McLamore (Box 25)
- - Kevin and Mary Fitzpatrick (Box 25)
- - Harry Mariani (Box 25)
- - Kenneth Himmel (Box 25)
- - Robert Zimmer (Box 25)
- - Louise O'Sullivan (Box 25)
- Dean's Distinguished Speaker List, 1990 (Box 25)
- - Madeline White (Box 25)
- - John Dixon (Box 25)
- - Larry Magnan (Box 25)
- - Toni Knorr (Box 25)
- - George Rice (Box 25)
- - Juergen Bartels (Box 25)
- - William Fisher (Box 25)
- - Jorgen Roed (Box 25)
- - Michael Leven (Box 25)
- - Robin Leach (Box 25)
- - William Sheppard (Box 25)
- - David Berins (Box 25)
- Dean's Distinguished Speaker List, 1991 (Box 25)
- - Frederick Mosser (Box 25)
- - Bjorn Hanson (Box 25)
- - Andrew Tisch (Box 25)
- - Ken and Marjorie Blanchard (Box 25)
- - Peter Burwash (Box 25)
- - James F. Mann (Box 25)
- - J. Erik Kamfjord (Box 25)
- - Valerie Ferguson (Box 25)
- - Merv Griffin (Box 25)
- - Patrick Terrail (Box 25)
- - Thomas Hulton (Box 25)
- Dean's Distinguished Speaker List, 1992 (Box 25)
- - Kenneth Hine (Box 25)
- - Michael Z. Kay (Box 25)
- - James Treadway (Box 25)
- - Jonathan Tisch (Box 25)
- - Caren W. Kline (Box 25)
- - John Norlander (Box 25)
- - Nils Nordh (Box 25)
- - John Nicolls (Box 25)
- - Ralph and Trish Nagel (Box 25)
- - R. David Thoams (Box 25)
- - Malcolm Goodridge (Box 25)
- - James Potter (Box 25)
- - Mark Parmerlee (Box 25)
- - Edward T. Pratt III (Box 25)
- Australian International Hotel School Correspondence, Pre 1994 (Box 26)
- Australian International Hotel School Correspondence, 1994 (Box 26)
- Australian International Hotel School Correspondence, 1995 (Box 26)
- Australian International Hotel School Correspondence, 1996 (Box 26)
- Australian International Hotel School Advisory Board, 1995 (Box 26)
- Australian International Hotel School Advisory Board, 1996 (Box 26)
- Dean's Distinguished Speaker List, 1993 (Box 27)
- - Joe Lavin (Box 27)
- - Steve Wynn (Box 27)
- - Don Coe (Box 27)
- - Joan Sills (Box 27)
- - Herman Cain (Box 27)
- - David McNicholas (Box 27)
- - Darryl Hartley-Leonard (Box 27)
- - David Hanlon (Box 27)
- - Larry Pimental (Box 27)
- - Akira Osawa (Box 27)
- - Ward Morehouse (Box 27)
- - Lawrence Geller (Box 27)
- Dean's Distinguished Speaker List, 1994 (Box 27)
- - Dean's Board (Box 27)
- - Ron Magruder (Box 27)
- - Michael Hurst (Box 27)
- - Curtis Nelson (Box 27)
- - Harish Pattni (Box 27)
- - Bus Ryan (Box 27)
- - Seiji Tanaka (Box 27)
- - Joseph Neubauer (Box 27)
- - Grace Leo-Andrieu (Box 27)
- - Al Schuman (Box 27)
- - Arthur Adler (Box 27)
- - Dick Holtzman (Box 27)
- - John Sharpe (Box 27)
- - Robert Mondavi (Box 27)
- Dean's Distinguished Speaker List, 1995 (Box 27)
- - Stephen (Chip) Conley (Box 27)
- - Arch Stokes (Box 27)
- - Gene Rupnik (Box 27)
- - Garritt Toohey (Box 27)
- - John Erickson (Box 27)
- - Melinda Bush (Box 27)
- - John Dodge (Box 27)
- - Atef Mankarios (Box 27)
- - Larry and Bruce Reinstein (Box 27)
- - Larry Woolf (Box 27)
- - Robert and Amy Cima (Box 27)
- - Keith Daub (Box 27)
- Augusta Simon (Box 28)
- William Chernish (Box 28)
- Morgan (Box 28)
- Howland Swift Normand (Box 28)
- Peckenpaugh Susan Kiner (Box 28)
- Craig Snow David (Box 28)
- C. Dunn Mark (Box 28)
- Fulford (Box 28)
- Susanne and Patrick DeGraba (Box 28)
- Norman F. Katz (Box 28)
- Russell Bell (Box 28)
- William Anderson (Box 28)
- Chuck Sayles (Box 28)
- Incoming Dean from JJC, 1990 (Box 28)
- IMHI Documentation, 1981-1989 (Box 29)
- IMHI Historical Documents (Box 29)
- IMHI, Pre 1991 (Box 29)
- IMHI Correspondence, 1992 (Box 29)
- IMHI Correspondence, 1993 (Box 29)
- IMHI Correspondence, 1994 (Box 29)
- IMHI Correspondence, 1995 (Box 29)
- ESSEC Library (Box 29)
- IMHI Graduate Exchange (Box 29)
- IMHI Deputy Director (Box 29)
- Search IMHI Strategic (Box 29)
- Audit (Box 29)
- Publications Audit, 1994 (Box 30)
- SHA Unit Plan - Annual Report Correspondence, 1982 (Box 30)
- SHA Unit Plan - Annual Report Correspondence, 1983 (Box 30)
- SHA Unit Plan - Annual Report Correspondence, 1984 (Box 30)
- SHA Strategy, Pre 1990 (Box 30)
- FPC, 1990-1992 (Box 30)
- Center for Hospitality Research Proposals, 1994 (Box 30)
- Center for Hospitality Research Symposium, 1994 (Box 30)
- Center for Hospitality Research, 1992 (Box 30)
- Center for Hospitality Research, 1993 (Box 30)
- Housing and Feeding the Homeless, 1991-1992 (Box 30)
- Housing and Feeding the Homeless, 1987-1989 (Box 30)
- Statler Foundation Research Grants (Box 31)
- Statler Foundation Teaching Internships (Box 31)
- Statler Foundation Visit to SHA, 1992 (Box 31)
- Statler Foundation Visit to Buffalo, 1993 (Box 31)
- Status Report, 1990 (Box 31)
- Statler Foundation Status Report, 1987 (Box 31)
- Status Report, 1986 (Box 31)
- Status Report, 1985 (Box 31)
- Status Report, 1984 (Box 31)
- Status Report, 1983 (Box 31)
- Correspondence, 1953-1969 (Box 31)
- Correspondence, 1970-1979 (Box 31)
- Correspondence, 1980-1984 (Box 31)
- Correspondence, 1985-1990 (Box 31)
- Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 31)
- Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 31)
- Dean's Distinguished Lecturer Series, 1996-1997 (Box 32)
- Dean's Distinguished Lecturer Series, 1998-1999 (Box 33)
- Statler Foundation Newspaper Articles (Box 34)
- Statler Foundation Auditorium Correspondences (Box 34)
- Statler Foundation Maintenance Fund (Box 34)
- EM Statler Chair (Box 34)
- Statler Foundation 5th Floor Addition (Box 34)
- Statler Foundation Agreements (Box 34)
- Ward Asbury (Box 34)
- Robert Koren Peter (Box 34)
- Crotty Em Statler (Box 34)
- Bio (Box 34)
- Statler Foundation Legal Documents, Last Will and Testament, 1934 (Box 34)
- Nevada Chapter CSH Meeting, 1993 (Box 35)
- NYC-CHS Event, 1994 (Box 35)
- London/Berlin/Cyprus/Delhi/Hong Kong/Canberra, 1994 (Box 35)
- AH and MA Convention/Boulders (Box 35)
- Minneapolis (Box 35)
- NRA Show and Minneapolis (Box 35)
- Paris IMHI Graduation (Box 35)
- New York City (Box 35)
- CHRIE Conference/Alumni Meeting (Box 35)
- American Association Annual Meeting (Box 35)
- Bob Burns Meeting (Box 35)
- Hotelie of the Year (Box 35)
- Advisory Board Meeting and Dinner with Marne Obernauer (Box 35)
- Weill Meeting (Box 35)
- Chiu Wedding (Box 35)
- Helen Nelson Funeral (Box 35)
- CIA Trustee Meeting (Box 35)
- South Bend/Osaka/Tokyo (Box 35)
- Hotel Show (Box 35)
- AAOHA/NYC/Boston (Box 35)
- Florida (Box 35)
- President's Circle Dinner (Box 35)
- San Francisco/Los Angeles (Box 35)
- ITB and CSH European Chapter Meeting (Box 35)
- ARAMARK Visit (Box 35)
- AH and MA Conference (Box 35)
- Advisory Board Meeting (Box 35)
- NRA Show (Box 35)
- Tower Club Dinner (Box 35)
- NYU Investment Conference (Box 35)
- IMHI Graduation/Asia Pacific Meeting (Box 35)
- Alumni Meeting in California and New York (Box 35)
- Hurlbut Dinner (Box 35)
- CSH Meeting-Mexico (Box 35)
- Hotelie of the Year (Box 35)
- Alumni Meeting in Chicago (Box 35)
- NY Hotel Show (Box 35)
- CSH Buffalo Event (Box 35)
- Boston Alumni Meeting and Holiday Party (Box 35)
- White House Conference on Travel and Tourism, 1995 (Box 36)
- Masters of Professional Studies, 1989-1992 (Box 36)
- Master of Professional Studies, 1993 (Box 36)
- Academic Affairs, 1992 (Box 36)
- Academic Affairs, 1993-1994 (Box 36)
- Career Services, 1991-1992 (Box 36)
- Career Services, 1993-1994 (Box 36)
- Drown Prize, 1991-1993 (Box 36)
- Drown Prize, 1994 (Box 36)
- Student Services, 1991-1994 (Box 36)
- Commencement, 1993 (Box 36)
- Commencement, 1994 (Box 36)
- Commencement, 1995 (Box 36)
- Commencement, 1996 (Box 36)
- HEC 71, 1996 (Box 37)
- HEC 70 (Box 37)
- SHA Public Affairs, 1991 (Box 37)
- SHA Public Affairs, 1992 (Box 37)
- SHA Public Affairs, 1993 (Box 37)
- PDP, 1991-1994 (Box 37)
- PDP, 1995 (Box 37)
- Executive Education, 1990-1991 (Box 37)
- Kaga City Symposium (Box 37)
- Executive Education, 1992-1993 (Box 37)
- Winegardner and Hammons (Box 38)
- Financial Management Search, 1989 (Box 38)
- Faculty Searches (Lundberg and Brownell), 1986 (Box 38)
- HR Search Committee, 1986 (Box 38)
- MOHR Area Search Committee, 1990 (Box 38)
- Statler Hotel Managing Director Search, 1987 (Box 38)
- MPS Director Search, 1989 (Box 38)
- Assistant Dean Executive Education (Chernish) Search, 1988 (Box 38)
- Leaders Magazine Conference w/SHA, 1995 (Box 38)
- Leaders Magazine Conference w/SHA Schedule of Events and Pictures, 1995 (Box 38)
- Leaders Conference (DAD Notes), 1995 (Box 38)
- Leaders Conference Correspondences (Box 38)
- Leaders Conference by CHR Theories, Discussions, Findings, 1995 (Box 38)
- Barnes and Roche Inc. (Box 38)
- Blue Mountain International Hotel Management School Australia (Box 38)
- University of Las Vegas at Nevada (Box 38)
- Mara Institute - Malaysia, 1994 (Box 38)
- Linder Hotels, 1994 (Box 38)
- Assistant Dean - Business and Administration (DeGraba), 1990 (Box 38)
- Dean's Advisory Council, 1981 (Box 39)
- Dean's Advisory Council, 1982 (Box 39)
- Dean's Advisory Council, 1983 (Box 39)
- Dean's Advisory Council, 1984 (Box 39)
- Dean's Advisory Council, 1985 (Box 39)
- Dean's Advisory Council, 1986 (Box 39)
- Dean's Advisory Council, 1987 (Box 39)
- Dean's Advisory Council, 1989 (Box 39)
- Undergrad Education, 1986 (Box 39)
- Undergrad Education, 1987 (Box 39)
- Undergrad Education, 1988 (Box 39)
- Undergrad Education, 1989 (Box 39)
- Dean/Provost Kennedy (Box 39)
- Dean/Provost Barker (Box 39)
- Dean/Provost Nesheim (Box 39)
- Dean/Provost Rhodes (Box 39)
- SHA Deans Council, 1982 (Box 39)
- SHA Deans Council, 1984 (Box 39)
- SHA Deans Council, 1985 (Box 39)
- SHA Deans Council, 1986 (Box 39)
- SHA Deans Council, 1987 (Box 39)
- SHA Deans Council, 1988 (Box 40)
- SHA Deans Council, 1989 (Box 40)
- DAS/PAC, 1989 (Box 40)
- DAS/PAC, 1990 (Box 40)
- FPC, 1985-1986 (Box 40)
- FPC, 1987 (Box 40)
- FPC, 1988 (Box 40)
- FPC, 1989 (Box 40)
- COPIA - American Center for Wine, Food, Arts (Box 41)
- Australian International Hotel School-Board Materials, 2000-2001 (Box 41)
- Beck Center Buttons (Box 41)
- Faculty Minutes and Supporting Documents: AY 76-93, 2004 (Box 42)
- Faculty Minutes and Supporting Documents: AY 94-01, 2004 (Box 43)
- Faculty Minutes and Supporting Documents: AY 01-02, 2004 (Box 44)
- Graduate Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1994-2003 (Box 44)
- Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2003-2005 (Box 44)
- Statler Chain Recipes from the 1940's and 50's, 2004 (Box 45)
- HEC Silver Letter Opener and Miniature Goblet (Box 45)
- Photos: (Box 45)
- Tom Pedulla, 1960 (Box 45)
- J.W. Marriott, 1986 (Box 45)
- Ground Breaking, 1987 (Box 45)
- Hotel Grand Opening, 1989 (Box 45)
- Dean's Distinguished Lecture Series, 2001-2005 (Box 45)
- Hotel Ezra Cornell 77 Including Contact Sheets, 2002 (Box 45)
- Faculty Retirement: Mac Noden, 2002 (Box 45)
- Faculty Retirement: Jack Clark, 2002 (Box 45)
- Faculty Retirement: Richard Moore, 2002 (Box 45)
- Faculty Retirement: Avner Arbe, 2002 (Box 45)
- Homecoming, 2002 (Box 45)
- Beck Center Ground Breaking, 2002 (Box 45)
- Orientation, 2003 (Box 45)
- Graduation, 2004 (Box 45)
- Cornell Hotel Society Annual Meeting in Beijing, 2004 (Box 45)
- "Holiday Inn University" - U-matic Tape, 1975; V-6840 (Box 45)
- Reaching Higher, 1994; V-7101 (Box 45)
- Cornell Icon of the Industry Awards Dinner Program, 2009-06-02 (Box 46)
- Cornell Icon and Innovator Awards Dinner Program, 2011-06-07; 2012 (Box 46)
- The Innovation Network Program, 2011-11-14 (Box 46)
- The Innovation Network Invitation, 2012-01-22 (Box 46)
- Dean's Leadership Series Programs, 2007-11-13; 2008-11-11; 2012-06-14 (Box 46)